I don't know, like, the true history of Carnival or what today is.
Can you inform my chat?
I'll tell you.
Okay, so, basically, when you play mass, our ancestors were mocking the Europeans that came over
because we weren't allowed to participate in the Masquerade Balls.
Today is also the day that the slaves were emancipated in Canada.
So, yeah, even though people are here to get a dagger of bear gals and get bear bubbles,
today is also about the emancipation and the freedom of slaves.
So, there's a meme behind the people.
Thank you for informing the people.
I appreciate that.
A lot of people don't know that.
So, have fun.
Thank you.
You know, enjoy yourself.
Stay safe.
Have you had Jamaican food yet?
I had jerk chicken.
Jerk chicken.
I'm about to go eat some more right now.
I love that.
Okay.
White people do not have to be everywhere.
You don't got to be in Carnival.
Do you understand?
You don't got to be performing in Carnival.
It literally has nothing to do with you.
Unless you are a descendant of the indigenous and or enslaved people of the Caribbean islands and Africa.
What are you doing?
What are you doing waving flag?
Carnival is not just a fete.
It is remembrance.
Watch from the sidelines.
Get your energy right.
Come and join me, Amanda Seals, this Wednesday, August 12th, and every second Wednesday at Comedy in Harlem for Radical Rhythms Experience.
Every month we come together to level up our vibration with music, humor, and each other.
Tickets available at ComedyinHarlem.com.